Sup everyone, T5 here with a very
special video. Today we're back here
again with the Wings Club. The magic is
back episode two. Last time we left off,
Bloom was just enrolled into school. And
by enroll like I I mean kidnapped by two
fairies and like
that that's about it. Like I don't
remember anything else. Like she made
some friends at school and they don't
really matter all that much. Like there
was this guy, there was these guys and
some like evil witch [__] But like
there were a lot of characters. Like I
can't honestly I can't name any of them.
My goal by the by the end of this show
is to be able to name at least three of
these little fairy [__] Like if I
can learn three of the names, I'll be
happy. I'll be satisfied. So the episode
kicks off with Bloom like getting in
trouble for what happened in the last
episode. But none of that matters
anymore because apparently there's the
ceremony or some [__] that happens every
year to decide whether you're a fairy or
witch. But let's be real. I mean, in our
fear, the W might as well be a B because
you ain't a witch. You a [__] Like if
you're a witch, pack your bags and go
home cuz like don't even bother showing
up to class cuz like everyone's going to
hate you anyway and you don't want that
so go home. So like Ami Bloom like
starts crying like a baby that like she
might be a witch. Like you can't make
this [__] up and she's already falling
for like the witches are bad story. Like
if they were if they were evil would
they even be there? Would they let them
in the school in the first place? So
yeah, like everybody every fairy is
racist, but that's not even the weirdest
part. Like out of nowhere, this this
leprechaun just walks on screen. And it
was at this point I realized I knew
nothing about Wings Club. Like I thought
I was watching about a cartoon about
fairies versus witches and then there's
just this little man. What are we doing
here? Like he's literally standing on
the desk. I mean I I can't back up now
cuz like I'm in too deep. You get what I
mean? So, like Bloom messes up a spell
in class and some of this monster and
the little man turns it into like a
little animal. After class, Bloom goes
up to him and keep in mind he's a
leprechaun. So, she has to look down at
him because again, he's a leprechaun.
He's like one foot tall. God, I hope he
is not a coin character. This show has
witches, but there's a dark all around
this man that I cannot pinpoint.
But oh my god, he thank God he is in
episode for one minute. I can't stand
this guy. I don't even know his name.
Whiz shits. Something like that. I don't
get I don't know. I don't give a [__]
Also, he drew a butt on the chalkboard.
Get him out of the school. After class,
Bloom runs into the best boy, Sky, at
the courtyard and he's just hanging out
with his sister and something I did not
know, he is a prince. Like, I like him
even more now. That is bitching. Also,
it it couldn't be any more clear. These
two these two are smashing. Like, they
are siblings, but I mean, after the
leprechaun guy, I guess casual incest in
Wings Club doesn't surprise me. And
they're like going out for Boba T
because, you know, this like 2025, but
that ain't why we're here. We are here
for one thing and one thing alone. very
racism. After having another one with
like AI or some [__] Bloom like decides
that she would rather go home and go to
a nor school than like be seen as a
witch. And honestly, I can blame her.
Like a witch? Ew. My god. If my parents
just bought me a bicycle, I wouldn't
want to be a witch, too. Like the minute
I saw the life come, man, I' I'd be I'd
be I'd be moving back home. I'd be going
back to planet Earth. That's another
thing. I don't even know if this planet
is even They keep calling it Earth. Oh,
no. They keep calling Blooms World
Earth. Is Alfia on Earth? So, after this
all happened, after like this sad music
video starts to play and she's walking
through the school halls, it's like sad
and [__] when she's thinking about her
friends in the Wings Club and Sky and
her laugh at Alfia. Need I remind you,
we're not even halfway through episode
two. And this is already happening.
Like, this is some end of season type
[__] And Bloom is already questioning
her whole laugh. Are you kidding me? She
doesn't have to do that for too long,
though. Cuz when you get to school, she
remembers.
Oh, they're my friends. So now she wants
to go back. Oh no, wait. Oh, no. No, I
got wrong. She didn't want to go back.
She got attacked by like Stormy, Darcy,
and Ai who wants to steal her powers or
some [__] This fight is crazy. Like
they have like thunderbolts going like
they are in a public school. Keep that
in mind. Hundreds of people. They do not
hear the sounds of literal thunderbolts,
raging storm clouds, and eye shards
exploding against the wall. It is
insane. Bloom is like rescued by this
like this person. I don't know. I don't
Did they say her name? I don't know. I
don't know. She's in the original. She
might be. I don't know. I think after
like she she showed up, she was Why did
she show up? She didn't do anything cuz
Bloom set the room on fire and instead
of and instead of like putting out the
fire with the ash, Aie and the other two
just run away and then Bloom's dad shows
up and he's he's a firefighter which I
don't know if they said that. Maybe they
did and I'm just not paying attention on
anything. I don't know. I don't think
they did. But yeah, Bloom's dad is a
firefighter, which explains why they're
so rich. Honestly, I was just confused
the whole time. Bloom tells her parents
that she's a fairy and they're like,
"Oh, oh, oh yeah, we know. We know. You
don't got to tell us that." It's not
like not a big revelation or anything.
They just like knew the whole time. I
wasn't really a fan of that. But yeah,
they could have had some really cool
like drama and [__] but they chose not
to do it. I don't give a [__] So like
the other Winxel members arrive and tell
Bloom that they miss her at school which
that's a lie because they didn't do
anything together and the one time they
were together they [__] they fought
because like Aisha I think dropped water
on Bloom and and then Techno was like
mad saying this party's done and they
all went their separate ways or some
[__] I just noticed something. They're
just eating lace potato chips, olives,
and is that a bowl of corn? I mean, it's
got to be because Bloom tries to pop
into popcorn, but last time I checked,
like I think you need like dried corn
for that [__] to make popcorn, which if
if it is, that just makes it even
weirder because that means they're just
eating like popcorn kernels. Also,
there's this little mistake that I I
wonder if anyone caught it cuz as far as
I can see, I'm the only one who did.
Like when I see like use like her spell
on like Bloom or some [__] to make him
mess up in class, for some reason the
symbol it's not her symbol. Like it's
like dowies. Like look at that. If you
like I don't know why they did this.
Maybe originally Dowsy was supposed to
use the spell, but because AI is like Bo
Bloom's rival, they need to like have
her do it. But forget all that. That's
not why we're here. We're here for the
moment we all wait for it. The ceremony
[__] the event that declares whether
or not you get rats. I like the power
where like lines up because you already
know where these like [__] are like
in trouble because like look at the
second one in line. She has no chance.
She is looking like a Kingdom Hearts
character. She, you know, she's not
going to be a fairy. She is going to be
a witch. her life is going to be hell
for the whole semester. But damn it, I I
respect it because at least she knows
what she's about unlike Bloom who's been
like a crybaby [__] this whole time and
her friends I'm not her friends like
cross the fingers praying to God that
she isn't a witch. Like are they going
to drop her like a sack of potatoes if
she is? I don't like the wings club.
They are not friends. I don't know why
they're doing this. And naturally the
the goth person in front of Bloom is a
witch. And that scares her. But
honestly, she takes like a champ. Not
Bloom, but the the one who declared a
witch. Like she just got declared a
witch. So there goes her rats. Like if I
was her, I thrown hands with Miss Pale
got a right then and there. But she
chose peace. She's a better witch than
me. Now it's like Bloom's turn. I mean,
this is why we all shut up. Like is
Bloom going to be a fail and continue
the cycle of hatred? Or would she be the
one to prove to Alfia once of all that
witches are all Oh no, she's just a
fairy. She is just a fairy [__] and she
is gonna continue like being a [__]
The crowd even starts cheering for which
oh my god that made me so mad. Why you
got to do that? If I was a witch, I'll
be out of the school. This is why
witches are evil. This is [__] I'm
sorry. After Bloom was done, it's like
time for Bloom's like evil twin brother.
But I I don't know why he's here because
this is like a ceremony for fairies and
witches. And as far as I can see,
correct me if I'm wrong, he is like the
only man within a 4 mile radius in the
scene. Also, when they judge him, they
say he's a warlock, which I thought this
ceremony was for witches. And I mean, so
yeah, that's episode two. Like, what are
we thinking, [__] Are we excited for
the inevitable showdown between Bloom
and like a bro? At this point, I I don't
really give a [__] So, yeah, that about
wraps up episode two of Winx Club. The
magic is back. I guess we got to ask
ourselves now like, is it getting any
better? And it it's getting there. Like
it's it's it's not it's not a 10 out of
10, but it's it's probably more like a
four out of 10. That's not that bad.
Like it doesn't mean I like it, but I
want to turn the TV off yet. You know
what? Actually, the leprechaun guy, I
think he's got a doctor about two
points. So, this episode, this gets two
Winxes out of town. Anyway, thanks for
watching, [__] If if you also want
to join the winks or some [__] like,
why not consider joining me on Patreon?
Like I don't really give a [__]
[Music]
A part of me is locked up in the past.
I'm always looking back and never really
disappear.
My heart is haunted by the memories.
the echores of your voice. I swear I can
still hear them sometimes.
I surrender to gravity.
Your gravity.
Why am I feeling so?
Everything is so cold. I'm in this now.
You're gone.
Someone help me.
[Music]
I still feel
I feel your presence everywhere I go. I
live in the sacraity.
[Music]
Why am I feeling so
everything
I'm
holding?
[Music]